[
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What large astronomical structure, consisting of stars, stellar remnants, gas, dust, and dark matter all gravitationally interacting?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "galaxy",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Due to its extreme gravity, which object possess an event horizon, a boundary beyond which events cannot affect an observer?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "black hole",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of a luminous giant star of low or intermediate mass in the late phase of stellar evolution, possessing a large radius and a relatively cool surface temperature?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "red giant",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of a dense stellar core remnant that contains mostly electron-degenerate matter? It shares a name with a magazine produced by Games Workshop.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "white dwarf",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which planet possesses an atmosphere approximately 90 times denser than that of the Earth, mostly made of carbon dioxide, and with an average temperature of 460\u00b0C, the hottest in the solar system?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Venus",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which two elements comprise approximately 99% of the Earth\u2019s atmosphere?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Nitrogen and Oxygen",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Karman line where by one convention outer space begins is at what altitude?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "100km",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Earth\u2019s atmosphere is typically divided into five vertical layers. Name three of them.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "troposphere, stratosphere, mesosphere, thermosphere",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Developed and named by James Lovelock, what is the name of the theory that all living organisms interact with their inorganic surroundings to form a self-regulating system for life on Earth? It\u2019s named after the Greek goddess of the Earth",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Gaia theory",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Crepuscular refers to animals that are predominantly active at which times?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "dawn and dusk",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Bioluminescence refers to the emission of what by a living organism?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "light",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which term refers to carnivores that primarily consume fish?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Piscivorous",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Protium, deuterium, and tritium are all isotopes of which element? The most abundant in the universe it possesses an atomic number of 1.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "hydrogen",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "a mixture of chemical elements of which at least one is a metal",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "alloy",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "a substance consisting of very large molecules called macromolecules, composed of many repeating subunits",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "polymer",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "a molecule that is seemingly repelled from a mass of water due to its nonpolarity",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "hydrophobe",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "At 64 degree North the most northerly capital city in the world is Reykjavik, capital of which country? Known for its stunning landscapes, active volcanoes, and winning the World\u2019s Strongest Man more than any other country?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Iceland",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Firstly for five, looking at the other hemisphere, which is the most southerly capital city in the world?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Wellington, NZ",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Situated in South America, which capital is at the highest altitude?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "La Paz, Bolivia",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Situated in central Asia, which is the coldest capital city in the world?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Bill Murray, Jim Carrey, Patrick Stewart, and Michael Caine have all played which un-festive character, the protagonist of an 1843 novel by Charles Dickens, in various screen adaptations?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Ebenezer Scrooge",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which famous street in Bristol is home to The Scrandit, Rova, and Chance & Counters?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Christmas Steps, Bristol",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Christmas Cross is an area in which English county? Its residents are known as Salopians",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Christmas Cross, Shropshire",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Turkey Island is an area in the City of Winchester, in which English county? According to the musical My Fair Lady, hurricanes hardly happen there",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Hampshire",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Lexical root of the words Kaiser and Tsar, which Imperial title comes from the name of a Roman dictator born in 100BC and dying in 44BC to multiple stab wounds?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Caesar",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "In the biblical narrative, which Roman emperor ordered the census that Joseph and Mary were returning to Bethlehem for?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Caesar Augustus/Octavian",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Bethlehem was in the Roman province of Judea, conquered in 63BC by which general, member of the first triumvirate with Julius Caesar and Marcus Crassus",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Pompey",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What was the name of the Roman festival held in mid-winter, featuring feasting, candles, and gift-giving? It takes its name from a planet in our solar system.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Saturnalia",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Kingdom of Lydia in modern Turkey was notable for being the first people to use what common form of currency, typically made from gold, silver, or copper?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "coins",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Down, Cork, Antrim, and Dublin are all counties in which European nation? It achieved independence from Great Britain in 1921",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Republic of Ireland",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Christmas tree in Trafalgar Square in London is a gift from which country every year in recognition of British support of that country in WW2? It\u2019s known for its fjords, electric cars, and oil industry.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Norway",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Limpopo, the Zambezi, and the Congo are all rivers in which continent?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Africa",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Nigeria, Ghana, and Kenya declared independence from Britain, the first Olympic gold medal was won by an African, and the first heart transplant was performed. What decade were these events in?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "1960s",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Wadai war between the French colonial empire and the Wadai empire, the end of Moroccan independence, and the German-British Battle for Lake Tanganyika. What decade were these events in?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "1910s",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Nelson Mandela is elected president of South Africa, the Rwandan genocide starts, and the first African is elected to be secretary general of the United Nations. What decade were these events in?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "1990s",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Memphis, Thebes, Akhenaten, and Cairo have all been capitals of which African country? Its history stretches back over 8,000 years",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Egypt",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Depicted as a falcon-headed man wearing a white and red crown, the god of kingship and the sky. Which Egyptian god are we referring to?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Horus",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The god of death, mummification, and the afterlife, depicted as a man with a jackal\u2019s head. Which Egyptian god are we referring to?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Anubis",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A creator god, patron of craftsmen and architects. Regarded as the father of the sage Imhotep. Which Egyptian god are we referring to?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Ptah",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201cPolitical power grows out of the barrel of a gun\u201d is a quote attributed to which 20th century Chinese leader, founder of the people\u2019s republic and chairman of the Chinese Communist Party from 1949 until his death in 1976",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Chairman Mao / Mao Zedong",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What was the name of the Imperial dynasty that ruled China from 1368 to 1644, renowned for its flourishing of culture, especially ceramics?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Ming",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Cao Wei, Shu Han, and Eastern Wu were the initial dynastic states during which period of Chinese history, featuring individuals such as Zhang Heng and Cao Cao lasting from 220 to 280AD?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Three Kingdoms",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What was the name of the final dynasty in Chinese history, ending in 1912 with the Xinhai revolution?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Qing",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "On the Origin of Species, Frankenstein, War and Peace, and Beethoven\u2019s 9th symphony were all published in which century? Characterised by vast social upheaval, European imperialism, and technological advancement.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "19th century",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201cThey are misunderstood, probably because most people don\u2019t know how to cook them properly\u201d is a quote from chef Todd English about which foodstuff, popularly consumed on Christmas day and taking its name from a European capital city?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "brussel sprouts",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Chopped Solanum tuberosum prepared in the oven in fat and commonly flavoured with rosemary.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "roast potatoes",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Similarly prepared in the oven, a specimen of the species Meleagris gallopavo",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Turkey",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A sauce made from meat drippings combined with a thickening agent, and other flavourings such as redcurrant",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "gravy",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Abu Dhabi, Sao Paulo, Singapore, and Monaco are all cities that have hosted which sporting event this year, won by Max Verstappen?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Formula One",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which sport was developed in medieval Scotland, having a name believed to come from a Dutch word for club or stick?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Golf",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201ca perfect combination of violent action taking place in an atmosphere of total tranquility\u201d was how Billie Jean King described which sport?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Tennis",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "BASE jumping - a form of recreational parachuting - was invented in the mid 20th century, with its name being an acronym of objects you can jump off. What do the letters B, A, S, and E stand for?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "buildings, antennae, spans, earth",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Snowflakes are shaped like which regular polygon? It takes its name from its six faces and six vertices",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Hexagon",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the category of cloud that is thin, white, and made of ice crystals, forming between 4 and 20 km in altitude.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "cirrus",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Ice crystals as snow and sea ice raise the Earth\u2019s average albedo. What is albedo a measurement of?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "reflectivity",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Graupel is the name for snowflakes that fall encased in rime. Alongside water, what is the other constituent of rime?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "salt",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Antikythera mechanism, the analytical engine, and the ENIAC were all early examples of what device, taking its name from an individual who performed calculations?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "computer",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "HCl, H2SO4, and HNO3 are all examples of what? I\u2019m looking for the name of a fluid that has a pH value of less than 7.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "acid",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which element is a key component of: photosynthesis, respiration, and oxidation?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Oxygen",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Chemical reactions can be exothermic, meaning they give off heat, or which other term, meaning to absorb heat?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "endothermic",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Atmospheric ozone was destroyed by the chemical unbalancing of the Chapman cycle by which collection of gases? I\u2019m looking for a three letter acronym.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "CFCs",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the geological process that transports sediment along a coast, dependent on the angle of incoming waves? It leaves behind features such as spits, tombolos, and bars",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "longshore drift",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Erratics, moraines, and drumlins are all landscape features left behind by the movements of what?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "glaciers",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the layer of the Earth bounded by the crust and the core, containing approximately 2/3 the mass of the planet?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "mantle",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What was the name of the planet-spanning supercontinent that existed between about 330 and 200 million years ago?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Pangaea",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Extremely rare today, which disease, caused by a lack of ascorbic acid in the body, was the scourge of sailors up until the mid-18th century? It can be treated with Vitamin C supplements.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "scurvy",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201ctwo bean-shaped organs located at the back of the abdominal cavity. Their function is to maintain the body\u2019s chemical balance by excreting waste products and excess fluid in the form of urine\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "kidney",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201cAn organ responsible for absorption of water and excretion of solid waste material.\u201d I\u2019m looking for a two word name here.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "large intestine",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201cA gland about six inches long shaped like a flat pear. It creates enzymes to break down foods\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "pancreas",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which continent is the second largest in the world? Featuring 54 countries, the earliest remains of humans, and the world\u2019s largest hot desert?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Africa",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The largest country in Africa, bordering Tunisia, Libya, Niger, Mali, Mauritania, Western Sahara, and Morocco",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Algeria",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The newest country in Africa, formed in 2011 and bordering Ethiopia, Sudan, the Central African Republic, the DRC, Uganda, and Kenya",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "South Sudan",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The most populous country in Africa, bordering Benin, Niger, Chad, and Cameroon",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Nigeria",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which play features the characters Count Paris, Mercutio, Tybalt, and Benvolio, being a tale of the Montagues and the Capulets?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Romeo and Juliet",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Three witches tell the a general that he will be King of Scotland. Encouraged by his wife, he kills the king, becomes the new king, and kills more people out of paranoia.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Macbeth",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Iago is furious about being overlooked for promotion and plots to take revenge against his General, the Moor of Venice. Iago manipulates the general into believing his wife Desdemona is unfaithful, eventually murders her, and then kills himself.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Othello",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The ghost of the King of Denmark tells his son to avenge his murder by killing the new king, his uncle",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Hamlet",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Feliz navidad, frohlich jule, and joyeux noel are all translations of which common expression in English?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Merry Christmas",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201cThe only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing.\u201d is a quote from which Ancient Greek philosopher, known for teaching Plato and appearing Bill and Ted\u2019s Excellent Adventure",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Socrates",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which experiment uses stylized ethical dilemmas of whether to sacrifice one person to save a larger number? It was made into a video game this year.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Trolley Problem",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A thought experiment asking whether an object which has had all of its original components replaced remains the same object references which classical Greek hero?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Theseus",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Achilles and the tortoise, the arrow paradox, and the dichotomy paradox are all thought experiments by which Ancient Greek philosopher?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Zeno (of Elea)",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Rum tum tugger, Macavity, Skimbleshanks, and Mister Mistoffoles are all characters in which Andrew Lloyd Webber production, made into a critically panned film in 2019?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Cats",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which musical first performed in 2015 features King George III, Angelica Skylar, and Aaron Burr?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Hamilton",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "First performed in 1971, and features Betty Rizzo, Danny Zuko, and Sandra Dombrowski?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Grease",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "First performed in 2006, which musical features Hermes, Orpheus, and Eurydice?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Hadestown",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The film Mary Poppins, released in 1964, stars which English actress in the title role, also known for The Sound of Music?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Julie Andrews",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "From 2004, Nine intertwined stories examine the complexities of the one emotion that connects us all: love",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Love Actually",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "From 1993, The film follows the misadventures of Jack Skellington, Halloweentown's beloved pumpkin king, who has become bored with the same annual routine",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "The Nightmare Before Christmas",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "From 1988, New York City policeman John McClane is visiting his estranged wife and two daughters on Christmas Eve.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Die Hard",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201cCromulent\u201d and \u201cEmbiggen\u201d are two words added to English language dictionaries from which TV series, starting in 1989 and set in the town of Springfield?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "The Simpsons",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Launched in 1975 and still running today, which American sketch show launched the careers of Tina Fey, Will Ferrell, and Bill Murray among many others?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Saturday Night Live",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The most widely pirated show of all time, which TV show suffered a catastrophic slump in its ratings in its final season?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Game of Thrones",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Running from 1993 to 2004, which sit com is set in Seattle and focuses on the two Crane brothers, played by Kelsey Grammar and David Hyde Pierce?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Frasier",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Considered to be the most influential art style of the 20th century, practiced by artists including Picasso and Braque, which style is typified by objects being analysed, broken up and reassembled in an abstracted, often geometrical form?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Cubism",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A technique for softening the transition between colours, named from the Italian word for \u201csmoke\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Sfumato",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A technique in which small, distinct dots of colour are applied in patterns to form an image, notably used by Georges Seurat",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "pointillism",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Meaning \u201clight-dark\u201d, the use of strong contrasts between light and dark, usually bold contrasts affecting a whole composition",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Chiaroscuro",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Giving Christmas presents in stockings is a tradition based on the life of which saint, active in the 3rd and 4th centuries, being the patron saint of children, travellers, and sailors?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Saint Nicholas",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which is the most grown fruit tree in the world, first cultivated in China in the 4th century BC?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Orange",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which sedimentary rock currently supplies about a third of all electricity through being burned?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Coal",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Said to be inspired by the original dowry gifts from Saint Nicolas, which present was invented in their modern form in 1920s America?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Chocolate coins",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Duck, reverse sweep, googly, and spin bowler are all terms used in which sport? It can be played in formats including five day international and T20.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "cricket",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which international cricket team is nicknamed the Baggy Greens?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Australia",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "In cricket what does the acronym LBW stand for?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Leg Before Wicket",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Possessing four legs and two arms, which mythological creature has the upper body of a human and the lower body of a horse? They are also known as the Sagittary",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "centaur",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Chronicles of Narnia feature several centaurs as protagonists. Who wrote that series of books?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "CS Lewis",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series, centaurs are restricted to live in which area?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "The Forbidden Forest",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "In Warcraft centaurs are depicted as the savage children of which demigod?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Cenarius",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Who was the second person to walk on the moon? They share a first name with a character from the Toy Story franchise",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Buzz Aldrin",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Aldrin was part of which program of missions, lasting from 1961 to 1972, and named after the Greek god of light, music, and the Sun?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Apollo",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the car-sized rover landed by NASA on Mars in 2012? It used a skycrane to lower itself to the surface in the last part of its descent",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Curiosity",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Dragonfly mission aims to put a flying drone on which moon of Saturn, famous for its thick atmosphere and lakes of methane?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Titan",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Project Hail Mary, Artemis, and The Martian are novels by which American author? Their surname is a barrier across a river used to control water level, found for example in the river Avon in Bath",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Andy Weir",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Author of Looking for Alaska, Turtles All the Way Down, and the Fault in Our Stars",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "John Green",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Author of Norwegian Wood, 1Q84, Kafka on the Shore",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Haruki Murakami",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Author of Noughts and Crosses, Black and White, and Pig Heart Boy",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Malorie Blackman",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What does RAM in computing stand for?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Random Access Memory",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What does LCD in computing stand for?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Liquid Crystal Display",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What does GIF in computing stand for?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Graphics Interchange Format",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is defined as 'the natural science that studies matter, its fundamental constituents, its motion and behavior through space and time, and the related entities of energy and force'?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Physics",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which physicist published the principia in 1687, laying out the law of universal gravitation?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Isaac Newton",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which physicist won two Nobel prizes in physics and chemistry, and discovered the elements Polonium and Radium?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Marie Curie / Sklodovska-Curie",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Author of 'A Brief History of Time' among other works, which British physicist died in 2018?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Stephen Hawking",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "San Jose, San Diego, and Los Angeles are the three largest cities in which US state?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "California",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Mesa, Tucson, Phoenix are the three largest cities in which US state?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Arizona",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Augusta, Columbus, Atlanta are the three largest cities in which US state?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Georgia",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Joliet, Aurora, Chicago are the three largest cities in which US state?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Illinois",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The European capital of culture in 2008, which city in the north of England is perhaps best known as the birthplace of The Beatles?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Liverpool",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which was the first capital of culture in 1985, famous for the Parthenon, the Panathenaic Stadium, and the Temple of Hephaestus?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Athens",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which Irish city was named capital of culture in 2005? It shares its name with an impermeable, buoyant material",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Cork",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "In which country in southeast Europe is Plovdiv, the winner for 2019? The city is known for its Roman ruins, Ottoman townhouses, and being the birthplace of wrestler Miroslav Barnyashev",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Bulgaria",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Born in Salzburg in 1756 which composer produced more than 800 works including Eine kleine Nachtmusik, The Magic Flute, and symphonies including the Jupiter Symphony?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Mozart",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which artist composed Swan Lake, the 1812 Overture, and The Nutcracker",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Tchaikovsky",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Goldberg Variations, The St Matthew Passion, and the Suites for Solo Cello are among the thousand plus compositions written by which German composer?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "JS Bach",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Doctor Atomic, Nixon in China, and A Short Ride in a Fast Machine. He shares a name with the second president of the United States.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "John Adams",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the series of video games based on the National Football League or NFL, published by EA since 1988? It takes its name from a hall of fame coach and commentator.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Madden NFL",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A cocktail made of two parts sparkling wine to one part orange juice",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "bucks fizz",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A drink traditionally made with milk, cream, sugar, egg yolks, and whipped egg whites, it has been described as \u201clurching around the glass like partially-sentient sludge\u201d?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "eggnog",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A fortified wine made from white grapes that are grown near the city of Jerez de la Frontera in Andalucia, Spain",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "sherry",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Gl\u00f6gg, Gl\u00fchwein, and vin chaud are all names for what drink popularly consumed around Christmastime, consisting of an alcoholic beverage being heated and spiced?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "mulled wine",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The rod of Asclepius is the symbol of which branch science, defined in antiquity by figures such as Galen, Celsus, and Hippocrates?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "medicine",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "According to ancient and medieval tradition the body was comprised of four elements in balance. Name three of them.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Blood, phlegm, black bile, yellow bile",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The first anaesthetic was nitrous oxide, better known by what name?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Laughing gas",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Penicillin, described as the first true antibiotic, was discovered by which Scottish physician?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Alexander Fleming",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The conference of the parties or COP is an annual summit on climate change, held last year in the UK and in which African country this year?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Egypt",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Prior to the industrial revolution the concentration of CO2 in the Earth\u2019s atmosphere was approximately 280 ppm. To the nearest 10 ppm what is the current concentration?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "420 ppm",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The continuous measurement of CO2 at Moana Loa in Hawaii since 1957 is known by which two-word name? I\u2019ll give you a hint, it includes the surname of a scientist",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Keeling Curve",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Lovely Bones, King Kong, and The Lord of the Rings were all directed by which film maker from New Zealand?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Peter Jackson",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Who directed the movies Point Break, The Hurt Locker, and Zero Dark Thirty?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Kathryn Bigelow",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Who directed the movies The Social Network, Seven, and Fight Club?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "David Fincher",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Who directed the movies Top Gun, Crimson Tide, and Man on Fire?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Tony Scott",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the architectural style defined by pointed arches, leading to the development of rib vaults and flying buttresses? It evolved from Romanesque architecture and was succeeded by Renaissance architecture",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Gothic",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which architect designed many iconic buildings in Barcelona including the Sagrada Familia, Casa Vicens, and Park G\u00fcell",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Antoni Gaudi",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the type of vaulting in which ribs are all of the same curve and spaced equidistantly? An example is the vaulting of Bath Abbey and Kings College Cambridge",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "fan vault",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the tallest building in the world, located in Dubai?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Burj Khalifa",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Taking its name from a Hawaiian word meaning \u201cquick\u201d which website was founded in 2001 by Jimmy Wales and Larry Sanger? It describes itself as \u201ca multilingual free online encyclopedia written and maintained by a community of volunteers\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "wikipedia",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Facebook was launched by Mark Zuckerberg in what year?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "2004",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Prior to 2017, how many characters long could a tweet be? I\u2019ll accept 5 either way.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "140",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "To which island nation does the .tv domain belong to, as used by for example Twitch?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Tuvalu",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the 12th element in the periodic table? It burns with a brilliant white light, has the symbol Mg, and is named after locations related to a tribe called the Magnetes.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Magnesium",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What are the bubbles in champagne - or other fizzy drinks - made of?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "CO2",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What substance makes Christmas trees green?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "chlorophyll",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Christmas crackers go BANG because of cardboard strips coated with gunpowder. Name any one of the five chemical elements present in gunpowder?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Potassium, Nitrogen, Oxygen, Carbon, Sulphur",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What name connects the following: a metal liquid at room temperature, the Roman messenger god, and the closest planet to the Sun?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Mercury",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Who was the Roman god of war, known as Ares in Ancient Greece?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Mars",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Known as Aphrodite in Ancient Greece, who was the Roman goddess of love?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Venus",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The god of time, wealth, and agriculture was known as Kronos in Ancient Greece and what name in the Roman Empire?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Saturn",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The largest country in South America, which nation was initially colonised by Pedro \u00c1lvares Cabral and declared independence from Portugal in 1822?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Brazil",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which 19th century revolutionary initiated the independence of six modern nations from the Spanish Empire and gave his name to one of them?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Simon Bolivar",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the royal citadel constructed by the Incas in Urubamba province, Peru? Its name is translated as \u201cold mountain\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Machu Picchu",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the earliest known major civilisation in South America, known for ritual bloodletting, potentially founding the mesoamerican ballgame, and the construction of colossal stone heads",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Olmecs",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The Battle of Bosworth Field was the last significant battle of which civil conflict, resulting in the death of King Richard the III and the crowning of Henry VII",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Wars of the Roses",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "\u201cA Family Comedy Without The Family\u201d is the tagline from which festive film from 1990, starring Joe Pesci, Daniel Stern, and Macaulay Culkin?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Home Alone",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which 1979 film had the tagline: \u201cIn space, no one can hear you scream\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Alien",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which 2000 film had the tagline: \u201cPoultry in motion\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Chicken Run",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which 1994 film as the tagline: \u201cFear can hold you prisoner. Hope can set you free.\u201d",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Shawshank Redemption",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Sgt Pepper\u2019s Lonely Hearts Club Band, The White Album, and Abbey Road are all albums released by which band, active from 1960 to 1970?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Beatles",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which band released the albums: A Night At the Opera, News of the World, and Innuendo",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Queen",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which band released the albums: Gang Signs & Prayer, Heavy is the Head, and This Is What I Mean",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Stormzy",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which band released the albums: Stadium Arcadium, Californication, and Blood Sugar Sex Magik",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Meaning \u201clack of bears\u201d in Ancient Greek, which continent is on average coldest, driest, and windiest. It was first observed in 1820",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Antarctica",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Comprising much of north Africa, it is bounded to the north by the Mediterranean Sea coast and to the south by the Sahel",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Sahara",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Approximately ten times smaller than the Sahara, which desert covers much of Botswana, and parts of Namibia and South Africa",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Kalahari",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Slightly larger than the Kalahari, which cold desert straddles the border of China and Mongolia",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Gobi",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Having an atomic mass of approximately one, a charge of plus one, and a spin of 1/2, which subatomic particle comprises atomic nuclei along with neutrons?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Proton",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Discovered in 1897 by JJ Thompson, which is the lightest of the leptons?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Electron",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Discovered in 1968 at the Stanford Linear Accelerator Centre, which elementary particle forms the building blocks of hadrons, and shares a name with a Ferengi character in Star Trek Deep Space 9?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Quark",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Discovered in 2012 at the LHC, which boson has been nicknamed \u201cthe God particle\u201d?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Higgs Boson",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Ursus maritimus is the Latin name for which animal, the largest living land carnivore?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "polar bear",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Equus asinus is the name of which animal that carried the Virgin Mary to Bethlehem",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "donkey",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Donkeys or ass, camels, and which other animal, Latin name Bos taurus, adored the infant Jesus in the carol In The Bleak Midwinter?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "ox",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Rangifer tarandus is the Latin name of which animal, popularised by a 1949 American christmas song?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "reindeer",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Written in 1965 by Frank Herbert, which novel takes place on the desert world of Arrakis, and was adapted into film multiple times, including by Denis Villeneuve in 2021?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Dune",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Written primarily by Rick Priestly and Bryan Ansell, this multi-media universe depicts a violent future Milky Way galaxy in which an Imperium of Man struggles to survive",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Warhammer 40,000",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Written by George R R Martin, this series of books follows figures attempting to control the continents of Westeros and Essos. I want the name of the whole series.",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "A Song of Ice and Fire",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Created by Hidetaka Miyazaki, this series of video games is set in a dark medieval fantasy world including the Kingdom of Lordran",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Dark Souls",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Genesis, The Epistle of Paul to the Romans, and the Book of Revelation are all components of which religious text, sacred to Christians?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "The Bible",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Queen Elizabeth the II who passed away in 2022, was the longest reigning monarch in British history. Born in 1819 who was the previously longest reigning monarch in British history?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Queen Victoria",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The first Battle of Bull Run, the Battle of Gettysburg, and the Battle of Vicksburg were all engagements in which conflict, lasting from 1861 to 1865 between the Union and the Confederacy",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "American Civil War",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Possibly the longest inhabited part of the United States, it became a state in 1867 when it was purchased from Russia",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Alaska",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which American state was founded in 1681 when William Penn received a royal deed from Charles II, displacing tribes including the Lenape",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Pennsylvania",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which American state is the first mainland realm of the United States to be settled by Europeans in 1513, ruled at first by the Spanish then the British",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Florida",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "A fruit bread coated with powdered sugar, stollen is the traditional fruit cake eaten at Christmas in which country?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Germany",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Named after a chef, not a ruler from the ancient world, which salad was invented in Mexico in 1924?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Caesar salad",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "Which popular dish - sometime referred to as a British national dish - is commonly believed to be from India but was invented in Glasgow in the 1970s?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Chicken Tikka Masala",
        "source": ""
    },
    {
        "category_id": "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE",
        "lang": "en",
        "tags": [
            "UNIVERSITY_CHALLENGE"
        ],
        "question": "The kipferl, a crescent shaped pastry from Austria is the inspiration for which more modern French dish made from laminated dough?",
        "answer": 0,
        "answers": "Croissant",
        "source": ""
    }
]